I Knew You Were Trouble
压制:随Feng
你是我的劫难
Taylor Swift
歌手
I think,I thank when it's all over
我想当一切都结束的时候
It just comes back and flashes,you know
它仍会在你脑海中闪现
It's like a kaleidoscope of memories
万花筒一般的记忆
which it all comes back
不断闪现
but he never does
但他从未回到我身边
I think part of me knew the second I saw him
我想当我第一眼看见他的时候
that this would happen
这一切都会发生
It's not really anything he said
不是因为他说了些什麼
or anything he did
或是做了什麼
It was the feeling that came along with it
而是一种陪伴在身边的感觉
and the crazy thing is
而最疯狂的是
I don't ever know if I'm gonna feel that way again
我甚至不知道我是否又投身於这感觉之中
But I don't konw if I should
也不确定我是否应该投身其中
I knew this wrold moved too fast
我知道世界瞬息万变
and burned too bright
燃烧光芒过甚
But I just thought
但我只是在想
how can the devil be pulling you towards someone who looks
恶魔是怎麼把你推向一个
so much like an angel when he smiles at you
笑起来像天使的邪灵
Maybe he knew that when he saw me
我想他在看见我时就已经知道答案
I guess I just lost my balance
我猜我失去了平衡
I think that the worst part of it all wasn't losing him
我想最糟的部份 并不是我失去了他
It was losing me
而是失去了自我
Once upon a time, a few mistakes ago,
在很久很久之前 当一切都是无容置疑的时候
I was in your sights, you got me all alone.
我在你的视线里 只身一人
You found me.You found me.You found me.
你寻寻觅觅地找到了我 是的 你找到了我
I guess you didn't care, and I guess I liked that,
我猜你一定毫不在乎找到我
And when I fell hard, you took a step back.
我深陷你的爱河里 而你在往后退缩
Without me Without me Without me
远离我 远离我 远离我
And he's long gone, when he's next to me,
他的心永不属我 即使他近在咫尺
And I realize the blame is on me.
我蓦然忆起所有问题都在我身上
'Cause I knew you were trouble when you walked in.
当你降临于我的生活时 我就知道你是我无法躲避的劫难
So shame on me now
现在只能深深地埋怨自己
I flew me to places I'd never been.
你带我私奔 流亡到一个我未曾落足的边际
Till you put me down.
直至你将从高空我推下
Oh, I knew you were trouble when you walked in.
当你走近我生活的那一刻 我就知道你是我无法逃避的陷阱
So shame on me now
现在只能深深地埋怨自己
I flew me to places I'd never been.
你带我领略我未曾浏览的风景
Now I'm lying on the cold hard ground.
而此刻 我却只能将心贴在在冰冷的地面
Oh, Oh
Trouble, Trouble, Trouble.
劫难 陷阱 无法躲避
Oh, Oh
Trouble, Trouble, Trouble.
劫难 陷阱 无法躲避
No apologies, he'll never see you cry,
没有半句道歉 他永远不会懂得你的哭泣
Pretends he doesn't know that he's the reason why.
装作未曾发生 毫不知情 他就是你哭泣至天明的原因
You're drowning You're drowning You're drowning
让你窒息 沉溺
Now I heard you moved on, from whispers on the street,
从大街小巷八卦听说你已移情别恋
A new notch in your belt is all I'll ever be.
而我只是你腰带上的一个小孔罢了
And now I see,now I see,now I see
此刻 我如梦惊醒
He was long gone when he met me,
他遇到我时我能感觉到他已心不在焉
And I realize the joke is on me.
我知道我对自己开了个天大的玩笑
Hey
I knew you were trouble when you walked in,
当你踏入我生活时 我便知道你是我的劫难
So shame on me now
现在我只能傻傻地埋怨自己
I flew me to places I'd never been,
你带我飞去 我不曾落足的边际
So you put me down.
直至你将从高空我推下
Oh, I knew you were trouble when you walked in,
当你走进我生活时 我便知道你是我的劫难
So shame on me now
所以现在我只能怪自己
I flew me to places I'd never been,
你带我看遍我不曾浏览的风景
Now I'm lying on the cold hard ground.
而此刻 我却只能将心贴在冰冷的地面
Oh, Oh
Trouble, Trouble, Trouble.
劫难 陷阱 无法躲避
Oh, Oh
Trouble, Trouble, Trouble.
劫难 陷阱 无法逃避
And the saddest fear, comes creeping in,
最悲伤的恐惧充斥我的脑海
That you never loved me, or her, or anyone, or anything, yeaaaa.
你不曾爱过我 也不曾爱过她 亦或是任何人 任何事情
I knew you were trouble when you walked in,
当你走进我生活时 我便知道你是我劫难
So shame on me now
所以错在自己
I flew me to places I'd never been,
你带我飞去 我不曾落足的角落
So you put me down.
直至你将从高空我推下
Oh I knew you were trouble when you walked in
当你走进我生活时 我便知道你是我劫难
So shame on me now
只能责怪自己
I flew me to places I'd never been.
你带我看遍 我不曾浏览的风景
Now I'm lying on the cold hard ground.
而此刻 我却只能将心贴在冰冷的地面
Oh, Oh
Trouble, Trouble, Trouble.
劫难 陷阱 无法逃避
Oh, Oh
Trouble, Trouble, Trouble.
劫难 陷阱 无法逃避
I knew you were trouble when you walked in.
当你走进我生活时 我便知道你是我劫难
Trouble, trouble, trouble.
劫难 陷阱 无法逃避
I knew you were trouble when you walked in.
当你走进我生活时 我便知道你是我劫难
压制:随Feng
Trouble, trouble, trouble.
劫难 陷阱 无法逃避
I don’t know if you know who you are until you lose who you are.
我不知道 如果你失去了你自己 你还是谁